Guide to the Stanford News Service Audiovisual Recordings SC1125
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Videorecordings, 1936-2011; Series 2
  - Sondius-XG, Satellite feed, Stanford-Yamaha Partnership, Master, 07/09/1997; 97-0709-4; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 18)
    Stanford University's Office of Technology Licensing (OTL) and Yamaha Corp. have announced a joint licensing program that comes close to cornering the intellectual market on a type of music synthesis called physical modeling. Physical modeling involves producing sound by generating a mathematical simulation of actual musical instruments, rather than modeling the sounds alone. The approach allows performers to duplicate the performance nuances, such as over-blowing or variations in vibrato, that are possible with real instruments. It also allows computer musicians and others to create and play new instruments that could never exist in nature, such as a flute played with a violin bow. The technology also can be applied to reproducing realistic sound effects, like doors slamming and cars screeching around corners.
  - Center for the Study of Language and Information, Archimedes - Tape 4, 05/12/1996; 96-0512-1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 19)
    CSLI - Archimedes 1996 The Archimedes Project was founded at Stanford University in 1990 as an independent research organization, It studies barriers to accessing and using information, computers, and information appliances and identifies and designs innovative solutions, including accessors, that advance universal access to and use of information and control of one's environment.
  - Center for the Study of Language and Information, Archimedes - Tape 1, 05/17/1996; 96-0517-1a; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 19)
    CSLI Archimedes 1996 End of Dr. Robert Walton interview; Laser eyetracker demos; Interview with Greg Edwards; The Archimedes Project was founded at Stanford University in 1990 as an independent research organization, It studies barriers to accessing and using information, computers, and information appliances and identifies and designs innovative solutions, including accessors, that advance universal access to and use of information and control of one's environment.
  - Center for the Study of Language and Information, Archimedes - Tape 2, 05/17/1996; 96-0517-1b; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 19)
    CSLI Archimedes 1996 Robert Edings; Mayer Max, project director; Shark National re-invention; The Archimedes Project was founded at Stanford University in 1990 as an independent research organization, It studies barriers to accessing and using information, computers, and information appliances and identifies and designs innovative solutions, including accessors, that advance universal access to and use of information and control of one's environment.
  - Center for the Study of Language and Information, Archimedes - Tape 3, 05/17/1996; 96-0517-1c; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 19)
    CSLI Archimedes 1996 Mayer Max, end interview; Cathy and Yoshi on two computers; Dr. Robert Walton working and talking to computer; Walton interview The Archimedes Project was founded at Stanford University in 1990 as an independent research organization, It studies barriers to accessing and using information, computers, and information appliances and identifies and designs innovative solutions, including accessors, that advance universal access to and use of information and control of one's environment.
  - Center for the Study of Language and Information, Archimedes - Tape 4, 05/17/1996; 96-0517-1d; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 19)
  - Center for the Study of Language and Information, Archimedes - Tape 5, 05/17/1996; 96-0517-1e; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 19)
  - Voice-Operated Computers, Mono Dub Master, 05/28/1996; 96-0528-1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 19)
    00:04:46
    CSLI (Center for the Study of Language and Information) [No further information on news story is available.]
  - CSLI, Voice operated computers, Master, 06/01/1996; 96-0601-1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 19)
    V/O recording, Audio Session with 3 takes, 0:16 (Take 3 was used.)
  - Stanford 1996 Commencement, 06/16/1996; 96-0616-1; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 19)
    00:07:50
    Mae Jemison, Founder and Director, Jemison Institute for Advanced Technology in Developing Countries at Dartmouth College, was the speaker. Mae Jemison SoundBites & B-Roll
  - Commencement - Tape 1, 06/16/1996; 96-0616-2a; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 19)
    Commencement 1996 Wacky walk; Faculty; Gerhard Casper; Mae Jemison, astronaut; Entry; Mae Jemison, Founder and Director, Jemison Institute for Advanced Technology in Developing Countries at Dartmouth College, was the speaker. 059 Bars; 59:48 Slate; 00:01 Entrance; 00:12 Gerhard Casper and Mae Jemison greeted by grads; 00:26 Balloon Cutaway; 00:29 Stanford President Gerhard Casper intros Jemison; 00:52 Jemison to the dais.; 01:00 Jemison say "Thank You."; 01:07 Cutaway Applause; 01:09 Jemison Sound Bite #1: "Reality is the world you are going into is people before you haven't been responsible..."; 03:35 Cutaway, Provost Condoleezza Rice; 03:40 Jemison Sound Bite #2: "The Challenge you face is to be prepared for change...."; 05:18 Cutaway applause; 05:29 Grads celebrating; 05:38 Flag; 05:46 Hugs; 05:57 Grad and Dad; 06:12 Picture taking; 06:19 Mom looks for graduating son; 06:27 Mom finds son; 06:35 Son hugs pal; 06:37 Hand in the air; 06:48 Jemison exits; 07:15 Stadium Banners; 07:24 Pan to Stanford Band; 07:34 Camera scans crowd; 07:49 Tape ends
  - Commencement - Tape 2, 06/16/1996; 96-0616-2b; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 19)
    Commencement 1996 Mae Jemison, Founder and Director, Jemison Institute for Advanced Technology in Developing Countries at Dartmouth College, was the speaker. Astronaut; Gerhard Casper introduction; Speech; Band
  - Commencement - Tape 3, 06/16/1996; 96-0616-2c; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 19)
    Commencement 1996 Mae Jemison, Founder and Director, Jemison Institute for Advanced Technology in Developing Countries at Dartmouth College, was the speaker. Mae Jemison, astronaut; Crowd frolics; Band
  - Stanford 1996 Commencement, Master, B-Roll & Mae Jemison Remarks, 06/16/1996; 96-0616-3; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 19)
  - 1996 Commencement 105, 6/16/1996; 96-0616-5; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 19)
    B-roll and Mae Jemison Remarks Mae Jemison, Founder and Director, Jemison Institute for Advanced Technology in Developing Countries at Dartmouth College, was the speaker.
  - National Marine Fisheries Service, Tagging Tuna, Dub, 06/26/1996; 96-0626-1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 19)
    00:04:38
    Cape Hatteras, NC Dub; Blue fin tuna surgical implant; 01:26 Tuna boats; 02:25 catching fish from ocean; 03:06 Block's boat; 03:36 Block's crew; 03:56 Close up tagging tuna; 05:01 Close up tagging tuna; 05:34 Tuna goes back in ocean
  - Richard Zare, Mars Rock Lab - Tape 1, July 15, 1996; 96-0715-1a; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 19)
    Interview with Richard Zare (rock samples) 1996 B-roll; Meteorite, ALH84001, was thrust into the limelight in August 1996 when a team of scientists lead by Professor Zare published a controversial analysis in the journal Science. They argued that they had discovered organic material, unusual mineralogical features and electron microscope images showing tiny oval and worm-shaped features that, when taken together, provided compelling circumstantial evidence that the meteorite was inhabited by Martian microorganisms more than three billion years ago.
  - Richard Zare, Mars Rock, Lab, July 15, 1996; 96-0715-1b; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 19)
    Professor Richard Zare interview end Simon Clemett; Zare and graduate student Simon Clemett - B-roll; postdoctoral student Xavier Chillier walks in; Copy cam - diagram; Meteorite, ALH84001, was thrust into the limelight in August 1996 when a team of scientists lead by Professor Zare published a controversial analysis in the journal Science. They argued that they had discovered organic material, unusual mineralogical features and electron microscope images showing tiny oval and worm-shaped features that, when taken together, provided compelling circumstantial evidence that the meteorite was inhabited by Martian microorganisms more than three billion years ago. Case contains a s
  - Underwater Tuna - Tape 1, 07/17/1996; 96-0717-1a; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 19)
    Underwater Tuna 1996 Tuna with satellite tag; Good tuna feeding in Big Tank; *00:52 Good tuna with tag overhead; 01:08 "Bob"; 01:36 Tuna overhead with tag; *01:49 Tuna overhead; 02:04 Tuna overhead; 02:14 Tuna swims by, tag visible; 02:32 CU tuna head; 02:36 CU tag; 02:58 Satellite tag hanging off of fish; 03:29 Fish swims out of edit; 04:27 CU tag; 04:58-05:03 Tag goes to pull out; 05:17 Tag on underside of fish; 05:42 CU tag on underside of fish; *08:59 CU tag; *12:59 Good radiant light above, tuna overhead; 13:18 CU tuna eye; 13:50-14:00 Clear shot of tag in tuna, groups of tuna; 15:28 Medium shot of tuna in tank; 16:35 Pool in the clear, POV tuna; 17:30 Shot tuna overhead; *18:26 Tuna speedboat shot, complete with bubbles; 19:02 Food hitting pool; 19:10 Fish go berserk; 19:19-19:23 Lots of food hits pool, tuna go crazy; 19:42 Tuna attack food; *20:14-20:17 Good feeding shot
  - Underwater Tuna - Tape 2, 07/17/1996; 96-0717-1b; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 19)
    Underwater Tuna 1996 Tuna jump/chomp; Open mouth; 00:08 Feeding frenzy; *03:22 Tuna with open mouth; 05:29 CU different tag - internal; 05:54-06:03 Good rotation from tuna on bottom of tank to looking up at outside; 09:33 Feisty tuna; 10:18 Compression shot; 11:20 Tuna attack food; 11:38 Good cluster of fish; 11:52 Tuna snatches fish close to frame; 12:10 Whirlpool as fish react to food; 12:44 Our friend the squid dies; *14:13 Tuna chomp; 14:51 Tuna chomp CU; 17:00 CU internal tag; 17:26 CU underbelly of tuna; 18:06 CU tuna; *19:38 CU underbelly and internal tag; 20:48 CU tuna head, lots of blue; 21:36 Feisty fish snap and water reflection; 22:56 CU external tag and side of fish; 23:47 Tag in the clear
  - Underwater Tuna - Tape 4, 07/17/1996; 96-0717-1d; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 19)
    Underwater Tuna 1996 Interview David Epel; B-roll Epel and graduate assistant; Melissa Kaufman; b-roll Block tuna tank. 00-21:18 David Epel Interview (see transcript). Epel B roll: *21:54 Left side Epel comes in picture and talks; 22:02 CU Melissa Kaufman; 22:28 Talking (replication); *22:45 Neutral shot, close-up microscope; *22:32 Right side Epel in picture, close-up; 23:02 Epel talks in the clear; 23:23 Melissa in the clear; 23:52 Epel through bottles; 24:03 Melissa through bottles; 24:31 Melissa through microscope; 24:34 Epel walks up and looks at microscope; *24:49 Closeup Epel through microscope; 24:55 Closeup Melissa. Tuna Lab - Above-water shots: 25:32 Woman with camera; 25:39 Wide shot tanks; 25:53 Medium shot Block; 26:04 Camera in clear; 26:22 Block; 26:42 Closeup Block; 26:59 Camera close-up; 27:02 Diver going in tank; 27:24 Tuna logo; *27:38 Camera in water with diver; 27:50 Block climbs ladder; *28:33 Shot of camera underwater; *29:25 Tuna take after food; 29:48 Dropping food; *29:55 Dropping food, close-up hand; *30:00 Tuna dive for food; 30:32 Wide shot tank; END
  - Underwater Tuna - Tape 5, July 17, 1996; 96-0717-1e; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 19)
    Underwater Tuna 1996 Interview with Barbara Block; Wetsuits; Interview with George Somero; B-roll Somero on beach; B-roll Bay Intertidal Zone; Somero in lab, going in; Somero students, icebox. 2:00:49-2:01:36 Block interview; 01:22 Block interview with divers behind her; 01:45 Silly license plate; 02:11 Bird rock; 02:26 Wetsuits, divers; 02:49 Diver takes a wetsuit; 03:01 Diver gear; 03:21 Cleaning gear; 03:49 Diver gear the other way; 04:04 Wetsuits walking down the line; 04:24 Surf; 04:35 Sea surf pulls out to dive suits; 05:20 Begin George Somero interview; 19:53 End Somero interview; 20:10 Kayaks; 20:14 Zoom starts, wide intertidal zone; 20:27 Birds with long necks, on bird rock; 20:58 Tour boat; 21:14 Birds and boats; 21:35 Boat out of frame, birds in clear; 21:59 Sea lion on rock; 22:07 Pull out; 22:09 Intertidal zone; 22:32 Somero walking with fishing pole; 23:25 Somero goes into office; 23:34 Somero in lab; 23:39 Gretchen in lab; 24:04 Graduate student; 24:34 CU Somero; *24:45 Nice talking between Somero and student; 24:55 CU machine notes; 25:36 Pan over lab; 26:09 CU Experiment; 26:22 Talking with student with Somero; *26:25 Neural shot of machine; 27:02 Somero's hands with printout; 27:13 Medium two shot, Somero and student; 27:27 CU student; *27:45 Good dialogue; 28:11 Angled shot, two shot between Somero and student; 28:22 Somero prepares to go in fridge - whole shot ends at 29:33; *29:01 CU ice fish
  - Underwater Camera, 07/18/1996; 96-0718-1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 19)
    Underwater Camera, Divers, Starfish, Monterey Bay
  - Stock Footage Order, Underwater Habitats and Squid Life Cycle, 07/19/1996; 96-0719-1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 19)
    00:07:00
    Sea Studios Tape Log 00:01 Space Galaxy shot, wide; 00:09 Shot of ocean crashing; 00:16 Fades into shop of kelp and plants swaying in ocean, medium shot; 00:37 Ocean waves slosh over plants
  - William Gilly, Baja, California, 07/20/1996; 96-0720-1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 19)
    William Gilly, Baja, California 1996 from July
  - Michigan Fish Hatchery, 07/21/1996; 96-0721-1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 19)
    00:10:00
    Michigan Fish Hatchery 3-sec pad front and back
  - Hopkins Marine Station, Egg Cases, Squid, Dub, 07/22/1996; 96-0722-1; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 19)
    Hopkins Marine Station July 1996 Egg cases; Squid; Mike (diver) interview; Audio; Hi-8 dub
  - Hopkins Marine Center Tape 1 (Tape #1), 07/28/1996; 96-0728-1a; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 19)
    Hopkins 1996 Zoom-ins and zoom-outs; Kelp bed and kayaks; Dennis Powers interview, continued on Tape 2; 00:29 Rubber boat with kids in intertidal zone; 00:47-00:54 Zoom out, extreme wide shot, intertidal zone; 01:01 Library; 01:20-01:45 Slow pull out to full shot of intertidal zone; 01:45-02:25 Intertidal zone push in to library; 02:34 CU kayakers; 03:13 Kayakers with intertidal zone behind; 03:31 CU kayakers; 04:51 Wide shot, kayakers and kelp beds; 05:49 People on rocks at tidepools; 06:17 Wide shot tidepools and intertidal zone; 06:28 Fishing boat; 06:37 Wide shot fishing boat and rec boat; 06:47 Tight shot fishing boat; 07:00 Fishing boat goes out of edit; 07:20 Denny Powers interview begins; Denny Powers: Cut One: 18:07-18:34 "People are science" quote; Cut Two: 20:40-21:12 "Buildings" quote; *Cut Three: 23:47-24:31 "Fishing" quote; Cut Four: 25:35-26:05 "Growth and Fish" quote; Cut Five: 28:31-28:55 "Food and Energy" quote; Cut Six: 29:05-29:14 "Aquaculture" quote; Cut Seven: 29:27-29:41 "Help the International Regulatory System" quote
  - Hopkins Marine Center Tape 2 (Tape #2), 07/28/1996; 96-0728-1b; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 19)
    Hopkins 1996 Interview with Dennis Powers concludes; Still lifes old classroom and samples (into 1940s, 50s, 60s, 70s); James Watanabe class; various shots; Portraits of students; Watanabe Clasroom black and whites - at 9:00 a.m.: 00:26 Ashley Simons at microscope; 00:34 Watanabe classroom; 01:11 Circle around classroom; 01:22 CU side shot student; 01:46 CU teacher's aide; 01:58 CU student; 02:09 CU pen writing; 02:26 Notes in clear, pulls out to classroom; Black and whites: 03:11 Still life, picture; 03:45 Wide shot picture of boatyard; 03:46 Long left pan; 05:40 Cannery Row; 06:50 Guys with fish; 08:41 CU Doc Ricketts; 09:40 Don Abbott; 10:22 Don "Izzy" Abbott (hit on glasses); 10:47 Rolf Bolen; 11:22 Colin Pittendrigh; 11:57 CU Pittendrigh; 12:33 Cornelis Van Niel; 13:30 W. G. Hewatt on rocks; 14:55 Title - Hewatt paper; 15:22 Date - Hewatt paper; 16:39 Flip through Hewatt paper; 17:39 Flip through again; 17:40 Hewatt picture; 18:30 Note to Japanese; 19:32 Timothy Hopkins; 19:51 Old marine station at Lover's Point, wide shot; 20:06 Begin right pan over station; 20:54 Wide shot; 21:30 Chinatown - burned; 22:49 Chinese fishermen; 23:00 Chinese fishermen with boats; 23:40 Wide shot boats; 24:07 Tight shot boats; 24:30 Houses on shore; 24:59 Stanford letter; 25:22 David Jordan; 25:42 Jordan letter; 25:50 Jordan signature; 26:35 CU Jordan picture; 27:03 Jordan signature on picture; 27:25 Old class lists; 27:57 CU student names on list; 28:11 CU remarks on list; 28:19 Flip list pages; 28:43 Flip list pages again; 28:56 CU remarks on list; END
  - Hopkins Marine Station- Tape 1 (Tape #3), 07/29/1996; 96-0729-1a; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 19)
    Classroom James Watanabe, concluding shots Black and whites; Shots 1-20: 00:33 Powers interview continues; 11:10-11:21 Quote, ocean; 11:23-11:48 Quote, ocean; 13:35 Old classroom; 13:52 Wide shot, old classroom; 14:15 Window shot, pulls out to wide shot classroom at 14:25; 14:34 Pan right onto window; 14:47 Wide shot window; 16:43 Sample in jar; 16:55 Close up sample; 17:21 Still lifes, samples from the 40s; 18:11 Still life, starfish; 18:19 Wide shot samples; 18:35 Close up samples - static; 19:08 Static wide shot of samples; 19:20 Old books; 20:07 Good statics of samples; 20:21 Pan right over sample shelf; 21:04 Medium close up pan; 21:35 Pan left; *21:44 Good statics of samples; 22:00 Silhouettes; 23:01 Silhouettes at microscope; 24:41 Watanabe sitting in class; 25:38 Wide shot classroom; 25:48-25:56 Pan from samples to classroom; 26:47 Watanabe at chalkboard; 27:08 Side shot Watanabe teaching; 27:41 Student portraits, writing; 28:13 Students paying attention, writing; 28:44 CU J.J. White; 28:55 Classroom shot and students; 29:33 Wide shot classroom; 29:53 Close up teacher's aide; 30:05 Close up Kevin; 30:23 Side shot students; 30:36 Close up blonde girl; 30;42 Students with Watanabe; 30:50 Watanabe; 30:54 Pan right to class; END. Denny Interview #2: 00:00 Start Denny Powers interview (continued); 01:50-02:12 "UV Dangers for kelp" quote; 04:18-04:31 "We are part of that food chain" quote; 05:39-06:02 "It's the kelp forest" quote; 06:19 Other end of quote; 09:21-09:53 "Huge reservoir" quote; END
  - Hopkins Marine Station - Tape 2 (Tape #4), 07/29/1996; 96-0729-1b; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 19)
    Black and white shots Doc Ricketts library exhibit; Loretta Roberson demo - interview concludes on T-5; Kelp and dye demo. 01:11 Stills of buildings; 01:24 Wide shot, boatyard; 01:45 Close up boatyard; 03:14 Lover's Point; 04:00 Beach and people; 04:17 Monterey Boatworks; 04:58 Close up Agassiz [building?]; 05:28 Wide shot marine station; 06:16 Old classrooms; 07:42 Samples in classroom; same shelves as in Watanabe's class; 08:48 Old lab shot; 10:07 Wide shot book; 10:41 Morris, Abbott and Hatterly; 04:11 Rickett's book; 12:20 Teva boat; 13:47 CU Izzy Abbott; 14:18 Cornelius Van Niel; 15:40 Jacques Loeb; 16:23 Lawrence Blinks; 16:53 Doc Ricketts exhibit; 17:12 Oceanography notebook; 18:59 Medium shot Ricketts; 19:54 Ricketts exhibit; 20:04 Interior of library; 20:07 Pan down to exhibit; 20:23 Pan up to library; 20:51 Medium shot Ricketts; 21:42 CU Ricketts; 21:53 Pan left; 22:14 Exterior of library; 22:48 Push in to library; 23:31 People walking in front of library; 23:48 People walking; 24:04 Push in to library door; 24:34 Kelp dye experiment; 25:00 Robeson's hands; 25:10 CU Robeson; 25:27 Robeson with dye; 25:55 Robeson puts dye in leaf; 26:12 Drop dye in water; 26:38 Wide shot with dye; 26:45 CU side shot; 27:49 Robeson interview. Robeson; 28:10 "Kelp shape" quote
  - Scenic shots, Classes, B-Roll, Master (5), 05/19/1997; 97-0519-3; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 19)
    00:13:15
    Scenery, Classes, B-Roll
  - Stanford Campus Views, undated; ZZ0242; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 20)
    00:05:00
  - Mars Rock Project, undated; ZZ0243; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 20)
    B-roll interview with Richard Zare B-roll interview with Simon Clement; Graphic Animation; Meteorite, ALH84001, was thrust into the limelight in August 1996 when a team of scientists lead by Professor Zare published a controversial analysis in the journal Science. They argued that they had discovered organic material, unusual mineralogical features and electron microscope images showing tiny oval and worm-shaped features that, when taken together, provided compelling circumstantial evidence that the meteorite was inhabited by Martian microorganisms more than three billion years ago. Stanford Mars Shot List: 1. Rock Sample; 2. Vacuum Chamber; 3. Console Adjustment; 4. Sample Inserted into Chamber; 5. Sample on TV Monitor; 6. Wide Shots and Cutaways of work area; 7. Laser Operation; 8. Rock being Lasered in Chamber; 9. Laser with audio "clacks"; 10. Close up Rock Glowing; 11. Wide Shot Chamber; 12. Oscilloscope; 13. Richard Zare B-Roll with Students; 14. Zare Sound (2 bites); 15. Simon Clemett Sound Bite; 16. Graphic Animation TRT:12 Seconds; 17. Text explanation of Animation
  - Stanford Mars Rock Project, undated; ZZ0244; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 20)
    Richard Zare Stanford Mars Shot List: 1. Rock Sample; 2. Vacuum Chamber; 3. Console Adjustment; 4. Sample Inserted into Chamber; 5. Sample on TV Monitor; 6. Wide Shots and Cutaways of work area; 7. Laser Operation; 8. Rock being Lasered in Chamber; 9. Laser with audio "clacks"; 10. Close up Rock Glowing; 11. Wide Shot Chamber; 12. Oscilloscope; 13. Richard Zare B-Roll with Students; 14. Zare Sound (2 bites); 15. Simon Clemett Sound Bite; 16. Graphic Animation TRT:12 Seconds; 17. Text explanation of Animation
  - Mars Rock Project, Master, undated; ZZ0245; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 20)
    It includes Laser Hits (on End)
  - Stanford GPS Tractor, VNR, Master, undated; ZZ0246; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 20)
    Tracked Video News Release (VNR), Clean version B-Roll, 2.26.26; A Stanford research team has equipped a John Deere tractor with a satellite-based automatic control system that can guide the 20,000-pound farm vehicle more precisely than the best human drivers.
  - Stanford GPS Tractor, No Supers, VNR & B-Roll, undated; ZZ0247; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 20)
    Tracked Video News Release (VNR), No Supers & B-Roll; A Stanford research team has equipped a John Deere tractor with a satellite-based automatic control system that can guide the 20,000-pound farm vehicle more precisely than the best human drivers.
  - Stanford GPS Tractor, With Supers, VNR & B-Roll, undated; ZZ0248; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 20)
    Tracked Video News Release (VNR), With Supers & B-Roll; A Stanford research team has equipped a John Deere tractor with a satellite-based automatic control system that can guide the 20,000-pound farm vehicle more precisely than the best human drivers.
  - McLaughlin Clan, B-Roll & Reception, undated; ZZ0249; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 20)
    [No information about this tape is available.]
  - Baker / Fruit Fly Gene B-roll & Slates, undated; ZZ0250; 1 videotape(s) (Betacam SP S) (Box 20)
    00:13:00